const STORE=[
    {
      question: "Harry Potter and the Sorcererâ€™s Stone (the book) was first published in the US in what year?",
      possibleResponses: ["1999", "2001", "1998", "2005"],
      correctAnswer: "1998",
      feedback: "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone (as it was called in the UK) was released a year earlier, but the book came out in the United States in September of 1998."
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following characters is a Hufflepuff?",
      possibleResponses: ["Molly Weasley", "Remus Lupin", "Nymphadora Tonks", "Luna Lovegood"],
      correctAnswer: "Nymphadora Tonks",
      feedback: "Nymphadora Tonks, the upbeat and brightly colored metamorphmagus, was in Hufflepuff during her time at Hogwarts."
    },
    {
      question: "How old is Harry Potter when he first attends Hogwarts?",
      possibleResponses: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
      correctAnswer: "11",
      feedback: "Though he is 10 at the start of the book, by the time Harry leaves for Hogwarts he has had his 11th birthday, which makes him eligible to begin his first year."
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these is the 4th book in the series?",
      possibleResponses: ["Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone", "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows", "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"],
      correctAnswer: "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
      feedback: "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire was the fourth book released in the series and came out in July 2000."
    },
    {
      question: "Out of these characters, who is the oldest?",
      possibleResponses: ["Ron Weasley", "Harry Potter", "Neville Longbottom", "Hermione Granger"],
      correctAnswer: "Hermione Granger",
      feedback: "Hermione's birthday falls shortly after the start of the school year in September, while Ron's is not until March. Neville and Harry bring up the rear with birthdays in late July."
    },
    {
      question: "How many sons do Arthur and Molly Weasley have?",
      possibleResponses: ["Seven", "Six", "Five", "Four"],
      correctAnswer: "Six",
      feedback: "Arthur and Molly have six sons - Bill, Charlie, Percy, Fred, George, and Ron."
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following characters is NOT a muggleborn?",
      possibleResponses: ["Hermione Granger", "Severus Snape", "Colin Creevey", "Justin Finch-Fletchley"],
      correctAnswer: "Severus Snape",
      feedback: "Severus Snape was in fact a half-blood, as his father Tobias was a muggle and his mother Eileen was a pure-blood witch."
    },
    {
      question: "What was the name of Harry's Mother?",
      possibleResponses: ["Lily", "Daisy", "Petunia", "Luna"],
      correctAnswer: "Lily",
      feedback: "Harry may have been raised by his Aunt Petunia, but his mother's name was Lily."
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a magical treat mentioned in the books?",
      possibleResponses: ["Treacle Tarts", "Pumpkin Pasties", "Licorice Wands", "Maple Macarons"],
      correctAnswer: "Maple Macarons",
      feedback: "Pumpkin Pasties, Treacle Tarts, and Licorice Wands were readily available from the snack trolly and at the Hogwarts feasts, but Maple Macarons are never mentioned."
    },
    {
      question: "Ron has a reputation for being good at which game?",
      possibleResponses: ["Wizard's Chess", "Quidditch", "Gobstones", "Exploding Snap"],
      correctAnswer: "Wizard's Chess",
      feedback: "Ron's incredible skill at Wizard's Chess plays an important role in the first book when the trio has to participate in a life-sized game of Chess to reach the Sorcerer's Stone."
    }
  ];